<xml>
<item>
<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Green Monster build for Matrix</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/86271.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=86271</link>
<summary>The Green Monster has smashed his way into K19. Logical layout with all the popular addons plus features and addons not seen elsewhere. This is a great build for a new user or a veteran Kodi master. With things not seen in many other builds like Plex, music, music, ats, cocodab and speed tester. Thanks to GM for this awesome build repos to wizards that have GM http://team-crew.github.io http://slamiousbuilds.com/repo http://funstersplace.net/funs </summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - FunsWizard themes and builds K19</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/85060.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=85060</link>
<summary>If you moved to 19 and struggling with which build to use here is one to check out. Funsterbe has several builds to choose from. The wizard offers some great features like cleaning tools, backup settings and a few others. Check out this great wizard and get your Kodi Marix 19 on repo http://funstersplace.net/funs/ </summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dabs Simple Build - Change Backgrounds</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/78306.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=78306</link>
<summary>There is a hidden feature in my builds where I make it easy to change backgrounds and offer a bunch. This video shows how easy it is to change the built in backgrounds or download some off my server</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>Adding an addon to DaBs Phenom build</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/78693.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=78693</link>
<summary>This video is my "1st CoCo Exclusive" haha.. This was requested by Ross who asked if I could show how to add addons to a build that did not include the addon he wanted. So this walks you through adding a addon via built in repo ( but i explain how to add a repo ) and create menu item for it. I also show how to add submenu and options within the skin to change location and name of item.</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have CmanNoX by Cman Build Showcase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79259.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=79259</link>
<summary>Lets take a walk through CmanNox build and see what it looks and feels like. I will walk you through most of the build so you know to expect if you decide to use it. Thank you to Cman for his work. Here is repo address: http://cmanbuilds.com/repo/</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have The LITE by Cman Build Showcase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79408.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=79408</link>
<summary>Lets take a walk through The LITE build and see what it looks and feels like. I will walk you through most of the build so you know to expect if you decide to use it. Thank you to Cman for his work. Here is repo address: http://cmanbuilds.com/repo/ </summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have Verdi build by EzzerMan Build Showcase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79422.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=79422</link>
<summary>Big thank you goes out to Ezzerman who gave me permission to do the showcase. This is a Aeon Nox skin that has been skinned to not even look like Nox. With traditional menu bar gone he gives you a 3 item menu bar offset with a complete green theme. Very unique that will run well on any device. Some links you may need: http://www.ezzer-mac.com/repo</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have Diablo Build by NaRcAcIsT Build Showcase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79554.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=79554</link>
<summary>I great looking and functional build by NaRcAcIsT. He has done tons of customization to this skin to give it a certain feel. Not over bloated with too many addons and sub-menu short cuts created to help you get to the content you want quickly. I want to thank him for his cool looking work and permission to do a showcase of it. http://narcacist.com/repo</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have The Green Monster Build Showcase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79878.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=79878</link>
<summary>This build is a bigger build but offers so much in a logical manner. In short time you will learn where your favorite short cuts are in the Green Beast. It has extra features like dedicated IPTV shortcuts, weather, sports, kids, few widgets and a ton of TRUSTED addons and repos. This is a 1-stop-shop build. Its a larger build so my not run great on devices with little space. Wizards that host build http://team-crew.github.io http://slamiousbuilds.com/repo http://funstersplace.net/funs</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have RedDawn build ShowCase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/80149.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=80149</link>
<summary>Thank you to Red79 for the permission to showcase this nice looking build. A small zipped build that packs a big punch on the amount of addons you get and options to find the content you want. Sections for Rd, 4k, non-RD, movies, tv, sports, kids and live tv. This build has nice looking widgets to make it easy to find new content. Thanks again. Links you might need http://cmanbuilds.com/repo/</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Must-Have Leia build by CDTV ShowCase</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/80532.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=80532</link>
<summary>This is CDTV Leia 4.4 version. This build pushes the limits of what a build can do and look like. The attention to detail is breath taking. The thought that goes into art, sounds, links, ease of use is amazing. CDTV I think is the oldest currently ( years build ) making builds today. His years show in his work and his builds. Thank you to CDTV for allowing me to show this great build. Great kodi build http://cellardoortv.com/repo</summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dabs Matrix 19 Help - cMan Kodi 19 wizard with build options</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82737.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82737</link>
<summary>This video is a bit long but i give you a quick glimpse of all the builds in this wizard (as of 3.8.2021). There is many options so if you are on Matrix 19 and want a build this wizard offers many options and looks. Thanks to cman, red79 and SG builds for their work with the builds. </summary>
</item>
<item>
<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Nature man NM19 build</title>
<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/83123.jpg</thumbnail>
<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=83123</link>
<summary>Nature man has released a Kodi 19 build full of some great addons. Come check it out and see if it fits your needs. Thank you to NM for allowing me to do a showcasing of his work. </summary>
</item>
</xml>